<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customers on SandMerit</title>
    <link>/customers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Customers on SandMerit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/customers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PHHP</title>
      <link>/customers/phhp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/phhp/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo; We have been working with SandFil since the year 2012.
We engaged SandFil for the Performance Management System and it was up and running successfully within a short amount of time. We have had experience in working with other providers, but SandFil&amp;rsquo;s passion in HRM solutions and sincerity in providing their services to their client is exemplary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte</title>
      <link>/customers/deloitte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/deloitte/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo; SandFil worked with Deloitte very well to implement the solution for our executive search practice.
From the outset, the team demonstrated an understanding of our eneds and worked collaboratively with us to establish an end product that met our requirements. Their consultants were easy to work with and were responsive to us as clients.
Andrew Lee, Executive Director
&amp;ldquo; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darton Management Recruiters (M) Sdn Bhd</title>
      <link>/customers/dr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/dr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo; We appreciate the SandFil software and technical support. They are attentive; understand our business processes, consistent in their follow-up and able to anticipate our needs in executive search industry. We have not come across any software error or major issues since we implemented the software early of the year.
We recommend SandFil to manage the tedious recruitment processes for the search industry.
Thank you.
Yours truly,
On behalf of Darton Management Recruiters,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPMG</title>
      <link>/customers/kpmg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/kpmg/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo; I would like to thank you for the excellent service that was rendered to KPMG for our recent web portal migration. The professionalism of your staff and the workmanship is above our expectation and we look forward to continue working with SandFil International on more future projects.
Regards,
Jimmy Wong, Senior Manager of Information Technology Services
&amp;ldquo; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GS Paper &amp; Packaging</title>
      <link>/customers/gspp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/gspp/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo; This is to confirm that we have been happy with SandFil implementation since the implementation was done in year 2007.
My team and I have been in contact with the research and development team in order to complete new installations for our career job portal and some ongoing upgrades. Throughout the project, the SandFil team was willing to go the extra mile to meet our needs and diligent in carrying out the work and solving issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>