<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SandMerit</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SandMerit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:30:15 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Employee Engagement &amp; Satisfaction Survey</title>
      <link>/features/employee-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:30:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/employee-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Studies have shown that organizations with high employee engagement are more productive and profitable than those organizations with low levels of engagement.
As such, we highly recommend you to conduct an Employee Satisfaction &amp;amp; Engagement Survey to uncover the hidden information, suggestions and insights you need from across your organization. Employee Surveys are the best, most cost-effective way to gather comprehensive information accurately from a large portion of your employees about how satisfied and how engaged they are, and what needs to be done to increase employee satisfaction, engagement and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talent Management Solutions</title>
      <link>/features/talent-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:30:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/talent-management/</guid>
      <description>If your organization is looking for comprehensive talent management solutions that include features such as
 Competency Management System,
 Performance Management System,
 Succession Planning System,
 Training Management System,
 E-Learning etc,  Please visit Sandfil.com for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year End Appraisal</title>
      <link>/features/year-end-appraisal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:29:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/year-end-appraisal/</guid>
      <description>In many organizations, employees fail to see how their work contributes to achieving the objectives of the company. Instead, departments, teams, and individuals focus on different things, on what the boss tells them is important or the company decides to target that year or the latest problem needing to be fixed. Rather than pulling together toward shared goals, they are pulled apart by shifting priorities and diverging objectives.
One of the distinguishing characteristics of our solution is how well it aligns people, plans, and processes with the mission and vision of the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>360 Assessment</title>
      <link>/features/360-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:29:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/360-assessment/</guid>
      <description>What is a 360 Assessment? The SandFil 360 Assessment is ideal for obtaining feedback for leadership development programs or as part of Performance Appraisal. It is where employees receive confidential and anonymous ratings and feedback from the people who work around them, such as employee&amp;rsquo;s manager, peers, and direct reports.
How will the 360 Assessement help my company? 360 Assessment helps to increases Self-awareness as the feedback report gives the employee and company insight into their behaviour and strengths, and how they are perceived by others in the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K&amp;N Kenanga</title>
      <link>/customers/kenanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 14:06:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/kenanga/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo; SandFil Performance Management System is an easily configurable product that can be adapted to align with and support the Performance Management model that we practise in the organisation.
The implementation and support team members have provided us with excellent service level when we started in early 2015 until today with generally less than 24 hours response time. The team members are competent, approachable and patient. We are happy with their service level and commitment to serve Kenanga thus far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IJM</title>
      <link>/customers/ijm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 14:02:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/ijm/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo; Dear Sir/Madam, I just want to thank SandMerit and SandFil International for their outstanding work. A conglomerate like us with mission critical applications need high standards of confidentially, availability, integrity and non-repudiation of database. SandFil International enabled us to implement the performance management system for 2,600 employees covering 4 business divisions within 2 to 3 months. As an appreciation to SandFil International, we will maintain long term relationship with them for our HR&amp;rsquo;s IT needs, since they are helpful, accommodating, approachable and very much committed to quality program development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyst Programmer</title>
      <link>/jobs/analyst-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/analyst-programmer/</guid>
      <description>Responsibilities and Requirements Shoot us an email at contact[at]sandfil[dot]com and we&amp;rsquo;ll talk.
SandFil International is a local leading Talent Management Technology and Consulting firm. In line with our oversea expansion and quest for quality excellence, we are seeking dynamic and career-minded individuals to grow with the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Consultant</title>
      <link>/jobs/technical-consultant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/technical-consultant/</guid>
      <description>Responsibilities  Conduct User Requirement Study (URS) on Software Projects
 System Configuration
 Communicate User Requirement with Software Engineers and Software QC
 Conduct User Acceptance Test
 Conduct Administrator Training  Requirements  Certificate/Diploma in Computer Studies or Information Technology.
 Candidate is required to have at least one year working experience in a software development environment.
 Good English communication skills is a must.
 Strong analytical and problem-solving skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Should You Join Us?</title>
      <link>/whyjoinus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/whyjoinus/</guid>
      <description>To put it simply, we&amp;rsquo;re a family.    Bali
      Beach trip
      Birthday celebration
      Birthday celebration (2)
      Bukit merah</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HR Consultancy</title>
      <link>/services/hr-consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 11:29:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/hr-consultancy/</guid>
      <description>We have a group of experienced HR consultants who can assist your organization to design a performance management framework.
 For more inquiries, submit the form below:  Salutation Mx Miss Mrs Mr   Name  E-mail  Contact Number Please enter your mobile or company number in either of the following formats: (011)222-3333 | 0390008888 | 011-222-3333   Company  Remarks     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Reward Employees</title>
      <link>/events/reward-employees-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/reward-employees-may/</guid>
      <description>                              1st
      2nd
      3rd
      4th
      5th
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In-house Training</title>
      <link>/services/inhouse-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 12:46:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/inhouse-training/</guid>
      <description>We understand the challenges faced by some organizations when setting up KPIs.
We have designed the in-house training programme specifically to help you learn the best way to set company KPIs for managers. Our HR Consultant will provide hands-on KPI setting training that are based on actual scenarios.
 For more inquiries, submit the form below:  Salutation Mx Miss Mrs Mr   Name  E-mail  Contact Number Please enter your mobile or company number in either of the following formats: (011)222-3333 | 0390008888 | 011-222-3333   Company  Remarks     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Training</title>
      <link>/services/public-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 12:46:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/public-training/</guid>
      <description>We host regular public workshops on KPI setting.
These public workshops will not only allow your managers to learn how to set KPIs, but also provide an opportunity for them to learn best practices from other organizations.
The workshop is conducted in an very interactive way, allowing for hands-on training.
 For more inquiries, submit the form below:  Salutation Mx Miss Mrs Mr   Name  E-mail  Contact Number Please enter your mobile or company number in either of the following formats: (011)222-3333 | 0390008888 | 011-222-3333   Company  Remarks     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRCA 2016</title>
      <link>/events/hrca-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrca-2016/</guid>
      <description>                              1st
      2nd
      3rd
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHHP</title>
      <link>/customers/phhp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/phhp/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo; We have been working with SandFil since the year 2012.
We engaged SandFil for the Performance Management System and it was up and running successfully within a short amount of time. We have had experience in working with other providers, but SandFil&amp;rsquo;s passion in HRM solutions and sincerity in providing their services to their client is exemplary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRCA 2015</title>
      <link>/events/hrca-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrca-2015/</guid>
      <description>                              1st
      2nd
      3rd
      4th
      5th
      6th
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRDF 2015</title>
      <link>/events/hrdf-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrdf-2015/</guid>
      <description>I m g 6250 min
      I m g 6255 min
      I m g 6256 min
      I m g 6259 min
      I m g 6302 min</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRCA 2014</title>
      <link>/events/hrca-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrca-2014/</guid>
      <description>                              1st
      2nd
      3rd
      4th
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRDF Kuching 2014</title>
      <link>/events/hrdf-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrdf-2014/</guid>
      <description>I m g 20141104 093247 min
      I m g 20141104 160957 min
      I m g 20141105 082349 min
      I m g 3088 min</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRCA 2013</title>
      <link>/events/hrca-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrca-2013/</guid>
      <description>                              1st
      2nd
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRCA 2012</title>
      <link>/events/hrca-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrca-2012/</guid>
      <description>                              1st
      2nd
      3rd
      4th
      5th
      6th
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte</title>
      <link>/customers/deloitte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/deloitte/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo; SandFil worked with Deloitte very well to implement the solution for our executive search practice.
From the outset, the team demonstrated an understanding of our eneds and worked collaboratively with us to establish an end product that met our requirements. Their consultants were easy to work with and were responsive to us as clients.
Andrew Lee, Executive Director
&amp;ldquo; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HR Tech Showcase 2012</title>
      <link>/events/hrtech-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrtech-2012/</guid>
      <description>                              I m g 1827 min
      I m g 1830 min
      I m g 1838 min
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRCA 2011</title>
      <link>/events/hrca-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrca-2011/</guid>
      <description>                              1st
      2nd
      3rd
      4th
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FMM HR Conference 2011</title>
      <link>/events/fmm-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/fmm-2011/</guid>
      <description>                              P1040217 min
      P1040221 min
      P1040224 min
      P1040237 min
      P1040243 min
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darton Management Recruiters (M) Sdn Bhd</title>
      <link>/customers/dr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/dr/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo; We appreciate the SandFil software and technical support. They are attentive; understand our business processes, consistent in their follow-up and able to anticipate our needs in executive search industry. We have not come across any software error or major issues since we implemented the software early of the year.
We recommend SandFil to manage the tedious recruitment processes for the search industry.
Thank you.
Yours truly,
On behalf of Darton Management Recruiters,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRCA 2010</title>
      <link>/events/hrca-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/hrca-2010/</guid>
      <description>                              1st
      2nd
      3rd
      4th
      5th
      6th
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPMG</title>
      <link>/customers/kpmg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/customers/kpmg/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo; I would like to thank you for the excellent service that was rendered to KPMG for our recent web portal migration. The professionalism of your staff and the workmanship is above our expectation and we look forward to continue working with SandFil International on more future projects.
Regards,
Jimmy Wong, Senior Manager of Information Technology Services
&amp;ldquo; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About SandMerit</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>From our past experiences in implementing comprehensive performance management systems for public listed companies and multi-national companies, we realized that small and medium size organizations are not ready to adopt such comprehensive solutions due to limited budget and resources to implement such systems.
SandMerit was designed to address the key challenges of managing people in an organization. For small and medium size organizations, ease of use and cost effectiveness are their concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Our HR Consultant</title>
      <link>/partner/consultant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partner/consultant/</guid>
      <description> Enter your contact details below  Salutation Mx Miss Mrs Mr   Name  E-mail  Contact Number Please enter your mobile or company number in either of the following formats: (011)222-3333 | 0390008888 | 011-222-3333   Company  Company Website    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Our Reseller</title>
      <link>/partner/reseller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partner/reseller/</guid>
      <description> Enter your contact details below  Salutation Mx Miss Mrs Mr   Name  E-mail  Contact Number Please enter your mobile or company number in either of the following formats: (011)222-3333 | 0390008888 | 011-222-3333   Company  Company Website    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Our Supplier</title>
      <link>/partner/supplier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partner/supplier/</guid>
      <description> Enter your contact details below  Salutation Mx Miss Mrs Mr   Name  E-mail  Contact Number Please enter your mobile or company number in either of the following formats: (011)222-3333 | 0390008888 | 011-222-3333   Company  Company Website    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> Feel free to contact us:
Malaysia Sales and Marketing Department  +603-7781-4097 | +603-7782-0966 | +603-7782-0968
Lot 9B, 9C, &amp; 9D (Level 1 - 3) Jalan PJS 1/27, 46150 Petaling Jaya, Selangor, Malaysia
  

Talk to Us  Designation Mx Mr Ms   Name  Email  Company  Phone number Please enter your mobile or company number in either of the following formats: 011-222-3333 | 0390008888   Remarks    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Invited</title>
      <link>/invite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/invite/</guid>
      <description>We are having seminars EVERY MONTH, come join us!  Join our FREE seminars to learn how to bring the best out of your company.  Enter your e-mail below and we&#39;ll contact you with more details.
 Presented by Datin Dr Wendy Liow Dean of ELM, HELP University
 Learn how to:   Identify and overcome performance management challenges    Reward and motivate employees (the RIGHT way!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>