<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on SandMerit</title>
    <link>/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on SandMerit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:30:15 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Employee Engagement &amp; Satisfaction Survey</title>
      <link>/features/employee-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:30:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/employee-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Studies have shown that organizations with high employee engagement are more productive and profitable than those organizations with low levels of engagement.
As such, we highly recommend you to conduct an Employee Satisfaction &amp;amp; Engagement Survey to uncover the hidden information, suggestions and insights you need from across your organization. Employee Surveys are the best, most cost-effective way to gather comprehensive information accurately from a large portion of your employees about how satisfied and how engaged they are, and what needs to be done to increase employee satisfaction, engagement and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talent Management Solutions</title>
      <link>/features/talent-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:30:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/talent-management/</guid>
      <description>If your organization is looking for comprehensive talent management solutions that include features such as
 Competency Management System,
 Performance Management System,
 Succession Planning System,
 Training Management System,
 E-Learning etc,  Please visit Sandfil.com for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year End Appraisal</title>
      <link>/features/year-end-appraisal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:29:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/year-end-appraisal/</guid>
      <description>In many organizations, employees fail to see how their work contributes to achieving the objectives of the company. Instead, departments, teams, and individuals focus on different things, on what the boss tells them is important or the company decides to target that year or the latest problem needing to be fixed. Rather than pulling together toward shared goals, they are pulled apart by shifting priorities and diverging objectives.
One of the distinguishing characteristics of our solution is how well it aligns people, plans, and processes with the mission and vision of the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>360 Assessment</title>
      <link>/features/360-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:29:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/360-assessment/</guid>
      <description>What is a 360 Assessment? The SandFil 360 Assessment is ideal for obtaining feedback for leadership development programs or as part of Performance Appraisal. It is where employees receive confidential and anonymous ratings and feedback from the people who work around them, such as employee&amp;rsquo;s manager, peers, and direct reports.
How will the 360 Assessement help my company? 360 Assessment helps to increases Self-awareness as the feedback report gives the employee and company insight into their behaviour and strengths, and how they are perceived by others in the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>